JADEY LI

(852) 5617 65 89 🕓

jadeyltli@gmail.com

www.facebook.com/jadeyli

Graduating with a Law degree in 2010, I have taken the knowledge and skills I have learnt and applied this to a business environment, helping businesses to thrive, whilst looking at things in a diligent manner. I am a passionate and hardworking individual, with a vision to succeed, With over 10 years of Business Development and Marketing experience, I also have great relationship building and sales skills.

BUSINESS DEVELOPMENT& MARKETING MANAGER

LANGUAGES

English Native proficiency
Cantonese Native proficiency
Mandarin Business proficiency

EDUCATION

LLB LAW

Northumbria University 2006-2010.

LEVEL 3 PUBLIC INTERPRETATION

Open Network University 2009-2010

SKILLS

Legal Research and Knowledge
Marketing
Business Strategising
Salesforce/ Infusionsoft
CRM Management
Microsoft Office



EXPERIENCE

CITCO, Hong Kong

Business Development & Mar Com Manager, 2016 – 2017

Responsible for new business sales to Multinational corporations, Hedge Funds and Private Equity funds across Asia.

Responsibilities include networking with new and existing clients across APAC, planning and building a sales pipeline, planning and management of events, writing and developing internal and external material for marketing and external communication purposes. Research into competitors and preparing analysis and reports. Knowledge and handling of AML and KYC.

CORVAIN, Hong Kong

Business Development & Mar Com Manager, 2015 – 2016 (Contract Based)

Market Entry planning into Asia for a Luxury Consumer goods company related. My responsibilities was to plan and execute the marketing and business development strategy for market entry into initially Hong Kong and across APAC. I was brought into the company to launch the product which included writing and planning digital content, Agency Management and management of marketing team, planning and installing window and retail displays. Production of trade and consumer events. Communication of brand messaging from a corporate level down to consumers and channel partners. Producing and presenting pitches to existing and new clients

Reason for Leaving: Contract ended

H Group International, UK

Director of Business Development and Marketing Communications , 2013 – 2015

Event Management company, heading up the Event production and overseeing the relationship building and commercial responsibilities. Looking at external communications, building presentations and pitches. Meeting with clients and scoping out new clients. Growing existing client accounts and

managing contractual obligations of partners. Building a pipeline of clients.

Reason for Leaving: Relocated back to Hong Kong

King & Wood Mallesons, HK

Paralegal, 2011 - 2012

Legal research and assistance with knowhow and special duties to projects and Disputes team.

Reason for Leaving: Team relocated back to Melbourne.

L'oreal

Account Manager, 2007-2011

Looking after different beauty counters in retail stores. Duties included looking after staff training, new product launches, operations of different counters, messaging, marketing, Event management, and full commercial responsibility of the counters. Full time employment whilst in Law school to build up commercial experience.

Reason for leaving: Moved back home to Northern Ireland after university